Brian Joo

Porcelain Sink Manufacturer



- 818-808-5601
- brianhjoo@gmail.com

Skilled Production Worker offering 8 years of experience in warehouse and manufacturing environments. Focused on being productive and safety-minded at all times. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.



Education

2012-09 - 2015-06

Bachelor of Science: Clinical Nutrition

California Polytechnic State University-San Luis Obispo - San Luis Obispo, CA



Work History

2014-04 - Current

Porcelain Sink Manufacturer

O'Brien Sinks, Paso Robles, CA

- Performed general equipment maintenance and repair to minimize downtime.
- Assembled products according to changing daily work orders and specific customer needs.
- Inspected finished products for quality and adherence to customer specifications.
- Oversaw logistics and inventory management for storeroom.
- Cross-trained existing employees to maximize team agility and performance.

AH-64D Helicopter Electrician

United States Army, Fort Bragg, NC

- Oversaw projects with crew of 6 soldiers maintaining, repairing, testing and calibrating helicopter electrical systems, components and equipment.
- Created status reports on helicopter maintenance and repairs while collaborating with team leaders to advance process initiatives.
- Read technical drawings, diagrams and documentation to make accurate decisions about electrical system repair work.
- Trained junior soldiers on proper maintenance procedures.

2004-07 - 2010-07